https://www.jazz.org/privacy/

ticketsAll Events2020-21 SeasonSubscriptionsDizzy's ClubSpecial EventsGroup SalesGift CertificatesHow to Purchase TicketsStudent TicketsJALC ShanghaiHow to Get HereAccessibilityNeighborhood DiningAccommodationslearnBand Director AcademyBusiness Leadership WorkshopEssentially EllingtonHigh School Jazz AcademyJazz for Young PeopleJunior Jazz AcademyMiddle School Jazz AcademySummer Jazz AcademySwing UniversityWeBopVisit Jazz Academywatch & listenLive WebcastsBlue Engine RecordsJazz AcademyRadio ShowsVideosPhotosStoresupportDonateMembershipSpecial EventsCorporate SponsorshipWorkplace GivingRentalsBlogaboutMissionHistoryLeadershipPress RoomAbout the JLCOPresenter's LoginPerformances and Tour DatesCareersContactFAQVenues
log in
connect
sign up
Follow Us
Join our mailing list to receive news, updates, announcements.
jlco
live webcasts
donate
donate now
Email
Contribution
tickets
Go
watch & listen
Live WebcastsBlue Engine RecordsJazz AcademyRadio ShowsVideosPhotos
store
support
join us
Membership
Young Patron Group
Special Events
Corporate Sponsorship
Workplace Giving
Privacy
Effective Date: March 22, 2019 This Privacy Policy describes the privacy practices of Jazz at Lincoln Center (collectively “Jazz,” “we,” “us,” and “our”) in connection with personal information we collect online (e.g., through our websites and mobile apps), and offline (e.g., at our concerts and events) (collectively, the “Services”). This Privacy Policy explains the types of personal information we collect, how we may use and share the information, and the privacy choices that you have with respect to our handling of personal information about you. Click on the links below to jump to the different sections of our Privacy Policy:How We Collect InformationTypes of Information We CollectAutomated Collection How We Use Your InformationHow We Share Your InformationOur Legitimate Interests Children's InformationYour Rights and Choices MarketingLinks to Other Websites and Third Party ContentInternational Data TransfersHow We Protect InformationRetentionChanges to Our Privacy PolicyContact UsHow We Collect Information We may collect personal information from various sources, including: • Directly from you • From third parties that organize events or programs at our facility • From our vendors and other third parties (such as advertisers, sponsors, etc.) • Automatically, from devices that you use to connect to our Services From time to time, we combine the personal information we collect about you with information from other sources. Types of Information We Collect The types of personal information we collect may include: • Contact information, such as name, email address, postal address, and phone number • Demographic information, such as date of birth, gender, and zip code • Content you make available through social media accounts • Billing information, such as credit card details and billing address • Membership information, including any information you submit in connection with your member profile • Information you include on a rental space application or on an application to enroll in one of our programs If you submit any personal information relating to other people, you represent that you have the authority to do so and to permit us to use the information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We may aggregate and/or de-identify data about visitors to our website and use it for product and service development and improvement activities. Automated Collection We, our service providers, and other third parties may also collect certain information about the use of our websites by automated means, such as cookies, web beacons and other technologies. A “cookie” is a text file that websites send to a visitor’s computer or other internet- connected device to uniquely identify the visitor’s browser or to store information settings in the browser. A “web beacon,” or pixel tag or clear GIF, is used to transmit information back to a web server. The information that may be collected by automated means includes: URLs that refer users to our websites Search terms used to reach our websites Details about the devices that are used to access our websites (such as IP address, browser type, and operating system information) Details about users’ interaction with our websites (such as the date, time, frequency, and length of visits, specific content and pages accessed and buttons clicked during the visits, and information provided by you, including email addresses) Web browsers may offer users of our websites the ability to disable receiving certain types of cookies; however, if cookies are disabled, some features or functionality of our websites may not function correctly. For more information on how to disable cookies, please visit your internet browser’s “help” menu or you can visit http://www.aboutcookies.org/how-to-control-cookies. Please note that not all tracking will stop even if you delete cookies. Because there is not yet a consensus on how companies should respond to web browser-based do-not-track (“DNT”) mechanisms, we do not respond to web browser-based DNT signals at this time. How We Use Your Information We may use the information we collect to:  Respond to your requests, questions, and comments  Manage ticket sales and group reservations  Offer products and services that we believe may be of interest to you  Fulfill, manage, and send you information about your orders  Offer and administer promotions, sweepstakes, or other contests  Provide you with newsletters, articles, announcements, invitations, and other information about concerts, programs, classes, and events  Provide and manage memberships  Collect and process donations  Offer educational and public programs  Analyze and enhance our communications and strategies  Tailor the content we display to website users in our communications, and in connection with the use of our Services  Process employment applications  Comply with legal requirements, judicial process, and our policies  Protect against, identify, investigate, and respond to fraud, illegal activity, and claims and other liabilitiesWe may also aggregate any personal information that we collect in connection with our websites, such that the information is no longer personally identifiable or attributable to you. We may use such aggregated information for our own legitimate business purposes without restriction, where permissible under applicable laws and regulations. How We Share Your Information We may share the information we collect about you with: • Others within our organization • Other members or donors • Other cultural organizations • Service providers that perform services on our behalf or others with whom we may collaborate (such as marketing organizations, payment processors, analytics organizations, technology providers, and other third parties with whom we jointly develop or offer programs or events) We may also disclose personal information to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation, protect and defend our rights or property, protect the safety of our visitors and website users or the public, or to protect against legal liability. Unless prohibited by applicable law, we reserve the right to transfer the information we maintain in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our organization or assets. If we engage in such a sale or transfer, we will – where required by applicable law – make reasonable efforts to direct the recipient to use your personal information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. After such a sale or transfer, you may contact the recipient with any inquiries concerning the processing of your personal information. Our Legitimate Interests We process your information given our legitimate interests in promoting our events and other offerings or to complete your requested transaction. We may also process your information given our legitimate interest in undertaking marketing activities to offer you benefits or services that may be of interest. Children’s Information We collect personal information from children in limited circumstances, such as for our Middle School Jazz Academy. However, when we collect personal information of children under the age of 13, we only do so with explicit consent of the child’s parent or guardian. We reserve the right to verify the parent or guardian’s identity prior to processing the personal information of a child. Your Privacy Choices If you would like to review, correct, update, suppress, restrict or delete personal information that you have previously provided to us, or if you would like to receive an electronic copy of your Personal Data for purposes of transmitting it to another company (to the extent this right to data portability is provided to you by law), you can contact us at privacy@jazz.org. In your request, please make clear what personal information you would like to have changed, whether you would like to have your personal information removed from our database, or other limitations you would like to put on our use of your personal information. We may reject your request, as permitted by applicable law. We reserve the right to verify your identity in connection with any requests regarding personal data to help ensure that we provide the information we maintain to the individuals to whom it pertains, and allow only those individuals or their authorized representatives to exercise rights with respect to that information. We will try to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable. Please note that we often need to retain certain data for record keeping purposes and/or to complete any transactions that you began prior to requesting a change or deletion (e.g., when you make a purchase or reservation, or enter a promotion, you may not be able to change or delete the personal information provided until after the completion of such purchase, event, or promotion). There may also be residual data that will remain within our databases and other records, which will not be removed. In addition, there may be certain data that we may need to retain and/or not allow you to review for legal, security or other reasons. Marketing We (or our service providers and advertising partners) may send you direct marketing communications and information about our products and services that we consider may be of interest to you. We will provide an option to unsubscribe or opt-out of further communication on any electronic marketing communication sent to you or you may opt out by contacting us as set out in the “Contact Us” section below. However, if you opt out of receiving such communications, we retain the right to send you non- marketing communications (such as information about your purchase or changes to our Privacy Policy). Links to Other Websites and Third Party Content We may provide links to other websites, services, and applications that are not operated or controlled by us (the “Third Party Services”). This Privacy Policy does not apply to the Third Party Services. While we attempt to facilitate access only to those Third Party Services that share our respect for your privacy, we cannot take responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of those Third Party Services. We encourage you to review and understand the privacy practices of any Third Party Services before providing any information to or through them. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the Third Party Service that provides the feature. International Data Transfers We may transfer your personal information for processing in countries other than the country in which you initially provided the information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. For example, if you are located outside of the United States, we typically transfer and process all personal information in the United States, where Jazz is headquartered. The countries to which we transfer personal information may not guarantee the same level of protection for personal information as the one in which you reside. By using the Services, you consent to the transfer of your information to the United States. How We Protect Information We maintain reasonable administrative, technical and physical safeguards designed to protect the personal information we maintain against accidental, unlawful or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, access, disclosure or use. Despite these efforts, however, no organization, including Jazz, can fully eliminate risks or guarantee the security of personal information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of information about you at any time, and we bear no liability for uses or disclosures of personal information or other data arising in connection with theft of the information or other malicious actions. Retention We retain personal information for as long as is necessary for the processing purpose(s) for which the information was collected, and any other permissible, related purpose. We may retain aggregated or de-identified information indefinitely. Changes to Our Privacy Policy We may at any time in our sole discretion revise or update this Privacy Policy. We will post any changes on this page and indicate at the top of this page the date this Privacy Policy was last revised. You may read a current, effective copy of this Privacy Policy at any time by visiting this page. We will also notify you of any material changes either through a pop-up notice, email or through other reasonable means. Contact Us Jazz is based in New York, New York and is the data controller responsible for your personal information. If you have any questions, requests or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at privacy@jazz.org or 3 Columbus Circle, 12th Floor, New York, New York 10019.
back to top | view all events
